Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Affiliated bodies correspondence and reports, 1907-1952; Series 2; 47 microfilm reels
  - Local unions correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Local #835, Gary, Indiana, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 30)
    - Local #836, Middletown, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 31)
    - Local #837, Galveston, Texas, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 32)
    - Local #838, Richmond, Virginia, 1939; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 33)
    - Local #838, Kansas City, Missouri, 1945-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 34)
    - Local #838, Kansas City, Missouri, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 35)
    - Local #839, Pasco, Washington, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 36)
    - Local #840, Vandalia, Illinois, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 37)
    - Local #841, Springdale, Arkansas, 1939, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 38)
    - Local #841, Boston, Massachusetts, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 39)
    - Local #842, Columbus, Georgia, 194 2-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 40)
    - Local #842, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 41)
    - Local #843, Newark, New Jersey, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 49, Segment 42)
    - Local #843, Newark, New Jersey, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 1)
    - Local #844, Fort Dodge, Iowa, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 2)
    - Local #845, Albert Lea, Minnesota, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 3)
    - Local #846, Panama City, Florida, 1942- 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 4)
    - Local #846, Boston, Massachusetts, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 5)
    - Local #847, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1945-1946, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 6)
    - Local #847, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 7)
    - Local #848, Los Angeles, California, 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 8)
    - Local #849, Fairmont, West Virginia, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 9)
    - Local #849, Oroville, California, 1946-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 10)
    - Local #850, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 11)
    - Local #851, Willmar, Minnesota, 1944-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 12)
    - Local #851, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 13)
    - Local #852, New York, New York, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 14)
    - Local #853, Alameda County, California, 1941-1946, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 14a)
    - Local #854, Brooklyn, New York, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 15)
    - Local #855, Gulfport, Mississippi, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 16)
    - (skipped), Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 17)
    - Local #855, St. John's, Newfoundlan4 Canada, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 18)
    - Local #856, Brazil, Indiana, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 19)
    - Local #856, Port Chester, New York, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 20)
    - Local #856, San Francisco, California, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 21)
    - Local #857, Sacramento, California, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 22)
    - Local #858, Galveston, Texas, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 23)
    - Local #859, Atlanta, Georgia, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 24)
    - Local #860, San Francisco, California, 1939, 1942- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 25)
    - Local #861, Olney, Illinois, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 26)
    - Local #861, Miami, Florida, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 27)
    - Local #862, Eldorado, Illinois, 1942-1944, n.d.; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 28)
    - Local #862, New York, New York, 1949, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 29)
    - Local #863, Newark, New Jersey, 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 30)
    - Local #864, Norfolk, Nebraska, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 31)
    - Local #864, Rolla, Missouri, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 32)
    - Local #865, Santa Maria, California, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 33)
    - Local #866, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 34)
    - Local #867, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1944, 1947, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 35)
    - Local #868, Reedsburg, Wisconsin, 1944, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 36)
    - Local #868, Kelowna, British Columbia, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 37)
    - Local #869, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 38)
    - Local #870, Richland Center, Wisconsin, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 39)
    - Local #871, Rapid City, South Dakota, 1941-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 40)
    - Local #871, Buffalo, New York, 1949-1951 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 41)
    - Local #872, Charleroi, Pennsylvania, 1941-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 42)
    - Local #872, Charleroi, Pennsylvania, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 43)
    - Local #873, St, Joseph, Missouri, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 44)
    - Local #874, Rochester, Minnesota, 1943-1944, 1947-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 45)
    - Local #875, Washington, D. C., 1945-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 46)
    - Local #876, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 47)
    - Local #876, Georgetown, Delaware, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 48)
    - Local #877, Birmingham, Alabama, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 49)
    - Local #878, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1942-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 50, Segment 50)
    - Local #878, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1946-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 1)
    - Local #878, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 2)
    - Local #879, Austin, Texas, 1942, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 3)
    - Local #879, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1946-1948, 1951-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 4)
    - Local #880, Windsor, Ontario, Canada, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 5)
    - Local #881, Parkersburg, West Virginia, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 6)
    - Local #881, Port Arthur and Fort Williams,Ontario, Canada, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 7)
    - Local #882, Seattle, Washington, 1948, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 8)
    - Local #883, Cambridge, Maryland, 1938; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 9)
    - Local #883, Peterborough, Ontario, Canada, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 10)
    - Local #883, Hood River, Oregon, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 11)
    - Local #884, Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 12)
    - Local #884, San Francisco, California, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 13)
    - Local #885, Brunswick, Georgia, 1944-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 14)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1941-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 15)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 16)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 17)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 18)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1947 -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 19)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1948-1949 /; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 20)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 21)
    - Local #886, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 22)
    - Local #887, Berlin, Wisconsin, 1945, 1948, 1950.; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 23)
    - Local #889, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1939-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 24)
    - Local #889, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1943-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 25)
    - Local #889, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 26)
    - Local #890, Salinas, California, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 51, Segment 27)
    - Local #891, Jackson, Mississippi, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 1)
    - Local #892, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 2)
    - Local #893, Detroit, Michigan, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 3)
    - Local #894, Wilmington, Delaware, 1938; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 4)
    - Local #894, Texarkana, Arkansas-Texas, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 5)
    - Local #894, Texarkana, Arkansas-Texas, 1944-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 6)
    - Local #894, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 7)
    - Local #895, Albany, New York, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 8)
    - Local #896, Cristobal, Canal Zone, 1942, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 9)
    - Local #897, Savannah, Georgia, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 10)
    - Local #897, Savannah, Georgia, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 11)
    - Local #898, El Centro, California, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 12)
    - Local #899 Birmingham, Alabama, 1942-1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 13)
    - Local #900 Pendleton, Oregon, 1948-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 14)
    - Local #901 Benld, Illinois, 1944-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 15)
    - Local #902 Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Scrapbook 16)
    - Local #902 Detroit, Michigan, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 17)
    - Local #903 DeSoto, Missouri, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 18)
    - Local #904 Honolulu, Hawaii, 19.45-1946, 1949- 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 19)
    - Local #905 Montgomery, Alabama, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 20)
    - Local #905 Denver, Colorado, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 21)
    - Local #906 Greenville, Mississippi, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 22)
    - Local #906 Columbus, Indiana, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 23)
    - Local #907 Union City, New Jersey, 1946, 1948- • 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 24)
    - Local #908 Lima, Ohio, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 25)
    - Local #909 Worthington, Minnesota, 1943-1945, 1948, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 26)
    - Local #910 Seattle, Washington, 1943-1944, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 27)
    - Local #911 Klamath Falls, Oregon, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 28)
    - Local #912 Salinas, California, 1945, 1948, 1950, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 29)
    - Local #913 Clarksburg, West Virginia, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 30)
    - Local #914 Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1950, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 31)
    - Local #915 Mobile, Alabama, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 32)
    - Local #916 Collinsville, Illinois, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 33)
    - Local #917 New York, New York, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 34)
    - Local #918 Ashtabula, Ohio, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 34)
    - Local #919 Newark, New Jersey, 1942-1944, 1948- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 35)
    - Local #920 Waupun, Wisconsin, 1944-1948, 1951- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 36)
    - Local #921 San Francisco, California, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 37)
    - Local #922 Alexandria, Virginia, 1944, 1948, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 38)
    - Local #923 Oakland, California, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 39)
    - Local #924 Cumberland, Maryland, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 40)
    - Local #925 Rochester, New York, 1943, 1946- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 41)
    - Local #926 Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 42)
    - Local #927 Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 43)
    - Local #928 Los Angeles, California, 1943-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 44)
    - Local #929 Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 52, Segment 45)
    - Local #930, Casper, Wyoming, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 1)
    - Local #931, Mt. Vernon, Illinois, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 2)
    - Local #931, Mt. Vernon, Illinois, '1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 3)
    - Local #932, Brandon, Manitoba, Canada, 1945-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 4)
    - Local #932, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 5)
    - Local #933, Rochester, New York, 1942, 1946- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 6)
    - Local #934, Harrisburg, Illinois, 1942-1946, 1949- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 7)
    - Local #935, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 8)
    - Local #935, Washington, D. C., 1945-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 9)
    - Local #935, Fort Francis, Ontario, Canada, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 10)
    - Local #936, Tuscaloosa, Alabama, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 11)
    - Local #937, Baltimore, Maryland, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 12)
    - Local #938, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 13)
    - Local #939, Key West, Florida, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 14)
    - Local #939, Boston, Massachusetts, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 15)
    - Local #940, Galveston, Texas, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 16)
    - Local #940, Galveston, Texas, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 17)
    - Local #940, Galveston, Texas, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 18)
    - Local #940, Galveston, Texas, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 19)
    - Local #941, El Paso, Texas, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 20)
    - Local #942, Los Angeles, California, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 21)
    - Local #943, Colorado Springs, Colorado, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 22)
    - Local #943, Huntingdon, West Virginia, 1949-1951 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 23)
    - Local #944, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 24)
    - Local #945, Lincoln, Illinois, 1941-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 25)
    - Local #945, Memphis, Tennessee, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 26)
    - Local #946, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1945-1946, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 27)
    - Local #947, Carbondale, Illinois, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 28)
    - Local #948, Coshocton, Ohio, 1941-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 29)
    - Local #948, Coshocton, Ohio, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 30)
    - Local #949, Houston, Texas, 1940-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 53, Segment 31)
    - Local #949, Houston, Texas, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 1)
    - Local #950, Hibbing, Minnesota, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 2)
    - Local #950, Scottsbluff, Nebraska, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 3)
    - Local #951, Tacoma, Washington, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 4)
    - Local #952, McLeansboro, Illinois, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 5)
    - Local #952, Moncton, New Brunswick, Canada, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 6)
    - Local #953, Kansas City, Missouri, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 7)
    - Local #954, Corpus Christi, Texas, 1941-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 8)
    - Local #954, Corning, California, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 9)
    - Local #955, Kansas City, Missouri, 1941-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 10)
    - (skipped), Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 11)
    - Local #955, Kansas City, Missouri, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 12)
    - Local #956, Kansas City, Missouri, 1941-1942, 1945- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 13)
    - Local #957, Dayton, Ohio, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 14)
    - Local #957, Dayton, Ohio, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 15)
    - Local #958, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 16)
    - Local #959, Anchorage, Alaska, 1942-1943, 1946-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 17)
    - Local #960, San Francisco, California, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 18)
    - Local #961, Pittsfield, Illinois, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 19)
    - Local #961, Denver, Colorado, 1947, 1950- 1952 /; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 20)
    - Local #962, Medford, Oregon, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 21)
    - Local #963, Bradford, Pennsylvania, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 22)
    - Local #964, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941, 1945- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 23)
    - Local #965, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 24)
    - Local #965, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 25)
    - Local #966, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1943, 1946-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 25a)
    - Local #967, Sarnia, Ontario, Canada, 1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 26)
    - Local #968, Houston, Texas, 1942-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 27)
    - Local #968, Houston, Texas, 1946-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 28)
    - Local #968, Houston, Texas, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 54, Segment 29)
    - Local #968, Houston, Texas, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 1)
    - Local #969, Lake Charles, Louisiana, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 2)
    - Local #970, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1944-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 3)
    - Local #971, Belleville, Illinois, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 4)
    - Local #972, Alton, Illinois, 1942-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 5)
    - Local #972, Crystal City, Texas, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 6)
    - Local #973, Lake Charles, Louisiana, 1940; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 7)
    - Local #973, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 8)
    - Local #974, Toledo, Ohio, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 9)
    - Local #974, Pensacola, Florida, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 10)
    - Local #974, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 11)
    - Local #975, St, Paul, Minnesota, . 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 12)
    - Local #975, St, Paul, Minnesota, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 13)
    - Local #976, Houston, Texas, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 14)
    - Local #976, Lethbridge, Alberta, Canada, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 15)
    - Local #976, Ogden, Utah, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 16)
    - Local #977, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1942-1947, 1950- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 17)
    - Local #978, Springfield, Missouri, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 18)
    - Local #978, Providence, Rhode Island, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 19)
    - Local #979, Corona, California, 1943-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 20)
    - Local #979, Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 21)
    - Local #980, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1939; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 22)
    - Local #980, Santa Rosa, California, 1947-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 23)
    - Local #981, Peru, Illinois, 1944-1946, 1949, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 24)
    - Local #982, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1941-1946, 1949- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 25)
    - Local #983, Pocatello and Idaho Falls, Idaho, 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 26)
    - Local #984, Granite City, Illinois, 1943-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 27)
    - Local #985, Detroit, Michigan, 1947, 1950- • 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 28)
    - Local #986, Los Angeles, California, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 29)
    - Local #987, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 30)
    - Local #988, Portsmouth, Ohio, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 31)
    - Local #989, Hannibal, Missouri, 1941-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 32)
    - Local #989, Pembroke, Ontario, Canada, 1947-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 33)
    - Local #990, Port Arthur and Fort William,Ontario, Canada, 1942, 1946, 1948, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 34)
    - Local #991, Mobile, Alabama, 1941-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 35)
    - Local #991, Mobile, Alabama, 1943-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 36)
    - Local #991, Mobile, Alabama, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 55, Segment 37)
    - Local #992, Hagerstown, Maryland, 1944, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 1)
    - Local #993, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1944-1945, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 2)
    - Local #994, Hot Springs, Arkansas, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 3)
    - Local #994, Los Angeles, California, 1948, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 4)
    - Local #995, Boston, Massachusetts, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 5)
    - Local #996, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 6)
    - Local #996, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 7)
    - Local #997, Washington, D. C., 1945, 1948, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 8)
    - Local #998, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 9)
    - Local #998, Corner Brook, Newfoundland,Canada, l949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 10)
    - Local #999, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1941, 1944-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 56, Segment 11)
  - Joint Council correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 2 Subseries 2